เยี่ยม ผมละโคตรแปลกใจเลย
คนบ้าที่ไหนกัน ที่มันเรียกที่นี่ว่าถนนชายป่า
แล้วอยู่ถัดมาอีกครึ่งกิโลจากซอยชายป่าเนี่ย
มันบ้ามาก.
ส่งผมมาที่เมืองเส็งเครง ที่โคตรงงแบบนี้
ผมคิดอย่างงั้นจริงๆ เมืองนี้แม่งห่วยมาก
โอเคที่รัก ไว้ค่อยคุยกันใหม่ บาย
โอเค ที่นี่ก็คงจะเป็นซอยไรน์
นี่แม่งอย่างกะเขาวงกต
โอเค ทีนี้ไปทางทิศตะวันออก
เดินตรงไปเรื่อยๆ แล้วก็...
คิดว่ามันบอกให้ไปทางซ้าย เมื้อกี้นั่นอะไรหน่ะ  นกยูง ?
เดินตรงไปเรื่อยๆ แล้วก็ทางซ้าย....
แค่เดินต่อไป อย่าทำอะไรบ้าๆเชียว แค่...
ฉันจะไปทางตรงข้ามก็แล้วกัน
ไม่ใช่วันนี้ ไม่ใช่กับฉัน
You know how much to take to address them motherfuckers, man. I am gone.
ไม่เอาน่าเพื่อน นี่มัน.. ช่วยด้วย
Quality over Quantity (QoQ) Releases
Get Out (2016)
ซิด...... ทางนั้นเป็นไงบ้าง
ดี
คุณมีแปรงสีฟันแล้วใช่ไหม ? อืม
ฮีบรูนี่คือสเปรย์ดับกลิ่นหรอ ? อืม
เสื้อผ้าที่ใส่สบายๆล่ะ ? อืม
แปปนึงนะซิด ฉันขอคุยกับพ่อแกหน่อย
อะไร?
พวกเขารู้ไหม ว่าผมเป็นคนดำ ?
ไม่
ต้องบอกหรอ ?
มันก็แค่....
เป็นสิ่งที่คุณควรจะ...
บอกเขา
พ่อคะ แม่คะ แฟนหนูเป็นพี่มืด และในสุดสัปดาห์นี้
คือหนูไม่อยากให้พ่อกับแม่ช็อคตาตั้ง เพราะแบบว่ามืด... คือมืด
คุณเคยบอกผมว่า ผมเป็นแฟนพี่มืดคนแรกของคุณ - ก็ใช่ แล้วมันยังไง ?
ก็มันเป็นสิ่งที่พวกเขาไม่เคยคาดคิดเอาไว้
ผมแค่ไม่อยากถูกปืนลูกซองไล่ยิงเอาที่สนามหน้าบ้าน
มันจะไม่มีทางเกิดขึ้นแน่นอน ข้อแรก พ่อของฉันโหวตให้โอบาม่ามา 3 ครั้งซ้อน
แล้ว ความรักมันเป็นอะไรที่จะจริงจัง
ฉันบอกคุณเรื่องนี้  เพราะมั่นใจว่าพ่อฉันคงต้องคุยกับคุณแน่
และมันอาจจะไม่สนุกสักเท่าไหร่
แต่สิ่งที่ฉันจะบอกคือ นี่คือเรื่องงี่เง่าของคนเป็นพ่อ
และพวกเขาไม่ใช่พวกเหยียดผิว
ฉันต้องบอกคุณไปแล้ว
ฉันจะไม่พาคุณไปบ้านหรอกถ้าเป็นแบบนั้น คิดดูสิ
ใช่ ผมรู้ - ดี
ไม่ ๆ ๆ ผมโตแล้วนะ - ไม่มีทาง
คุณหักบุหรี่ผมเหรอ?
เอาจริงดิ โยนทิ้งไปเลยเนี่ยนะ
นั่นมันเหรียญนึงเลยนะ เออคุณเพิ่งโยนเงินเหรียญนึงทิ้งไป
อืม นั่นมันเงินหนึ่งเหรียญที่คุณจ่ายเพื่อ นิโคติน
เออ ผมต้องโทรหา ร็อด
อย่า อย่าพูดอย่างงี้
เป็นไงบ้าง
ทำงานอยู่เหรอ - ใช่
เออ คริส ช่วยชั้นคิดหน่อยดิ
ทำไมชั้นถึงซวยในการที่ไปขอตรวจค้นผู้หญิงแก่วะ? มันก็ขั้นตอนทั่วไป
Gary believes that as a hag is old, they can hijack aircraft.
นั่น,เดี๋ยว,ไม่,ฉันรู้,คุณกำลังหัวเราะนะ
ฉันซีเรียสนะ ,เฮ้ย ,ต่อไป 9/11 เกิดจากความยุ่งยากคนแก่น่ะ
ขอบคุณสำหรับวันหยุดนี้นะแซด แล้วก็อย่าลืมกินอะไรบ้างละ
เขาเป็นดร.น่ะ ,ไม่เชื่อในตัวฉันเท่าไร
อ่าฮะ ฉันลืมอะไร เธอล่ะ
No, I accept your apology. It's okay.
มิสโรดเป็นไงไงบ้าง , ก็โอเค เธอนั่งอยู่น่ะ
พร้อจะคุยกับเขายัง - ไม่
ขอคุยกับเขาหน่อยได้ไหม
รอแปปนึง
ไฮ โรด แกรู้ว่าแกเลือกคนผิด
แหงละ มันก็แค่เทคนิคเล็กน้อยที่จะตบตา
ยังไม่สายเกินไปสำหรับเรา -โอเค-ได้
มันไม่ใช้ประเด็น เพราะเธอไม่ทำตามคำแนะนำ
แล้ว?
แล้วไม่ไปกับครอบครัวของสาวผิดขาวละ
What does she, lick your balls or something?
ใช่ บาย เธอรู้ใช้ไหมว่าฉันพูดอะไรคริส?
That bastard hung up.
เธอมันขี้อิฉา ไม่ฉันไม่อิฉา
I made you jealous. It's Rod. - I'm not jealous of Rod.
ทุกอย่างยังดี  ใช่ฉันเคยกลัวศพน่ะ เธอละ
อืม ฉันสบายดี
อยู่นี่นะ อะไรอะไรจะไปไหน
ไม่รู้ ฉัน....
อาจจะไปแถวนี้
ในอนาคต เธอเธอจะได้รับสิบแบบคนอเมริกัน
เออ โทษดี แค่สับสน
แล้วจะออกจากเมืองนี้หรอ
อ่าฮะ ครอบครัวฉันมาจาก เลคพอนตาโค พวกเขาขับรถมาในวันหยุดสุดสัปดาห์นี้
คุณครับ ผมขอดูใบขับขี่หน่อยได้มั้ยครับ? - เดี๋ยวค่ะ ดูทำไม?
ผมมีเป็นบัตรประชาชนครับ
ไม่ ก็เค้าไม่ได้เป็นคนขับ
ผมไม่ได้ถามว่าใครขับ ผมแค่อยากขอดูบัตรของเขา
ค่ะ แต่เพื่อ? ไม่เห็นจะมีเหตุผลเลย - นี่ครับ
ไม่ต้อง คุณไม่จำเป็นต้องเอาให้ดู คุณไม่ได้ทำอะไรผิด
ที่รัก ไม่เห็นเป็นไรเลย
ทุกครั้งที่เกิดอุบัติเหตุ พวกผมมีสิทธิ์ที่จะขอดู... - ไร้สาระ
คุณครับ........
ทุกอย่างโอเคมั้ย ไรอัน?
โอเค
ไปซ่อมไฟหน้า กับกระจกด้วย
ขอบคุณค่ะคุณตำรวจ
อะไร? - เมื่อกี้เซ็กซี่จัง
ฉันไม่ยอมให้ใครมายุ่งกะแฟนฉันหรอก
เข้าใจแล้ว
ถึงแล้ว
นี่คนสวนบ้านเรา
พร้อมรึยังคะ
หวัดดี ลูกใครเนี่ย มา ๆ
เป็นไงบ้าง รักพ่อเหมือนกันค่ะ คิดถึงมากเลย
นี่พ่อฉัน  ดีน  นี่ คริส ค่ะ
เรียกฉันว่าคุณอาร์มิเทจ....
ล้อเล่นน่า เรียกฉันว่าดีนได้เลย มาขอกอดหน่อย
เป็นไงบ้าง - ดีค่ะ แล้วคุณล่ะ
เราเป็นพวกชอบกอดสินะ - ใช่
นี่แม่ฉันค่ะ แม่คะ นี่คริส
ยินดีต้อนรับจ้ะ
ยินดีที่ได้เจอนะ
พ่อลูกดูตื่นเต้นมาก...
มา เข้ามาก่อน  ยินดีต้อนรับเข้าสู่บ้านเรานะจ้ะ
ขับรถมาเป็นไงบ้าง - ก็โอเคค่ะ
ที่จริงเราจนกวางไปตัวนึง - อะไรนะ?
มันตายมั้ย? - ตายค่ะ
โห แย่จัง แล้วลูกเป็นอะไรมั้ย
เราแค่ตกใจกันสุด ๆ แค่นั้นค่ะ - จริงเหรอ
ใช่ อยู่ดีๆ มันโผล่มาจากไหนก็ไม่รู้ครับ ชนแรงมาก
พวกลูกคงช็อกมาก
แปลกแบบโหด ๆ ดี แต่ลูกรู้อะไรมั้ย
พ่อว่า ตายไปตัวนึง ยังเหลืออีกหลายร้อย หลายพันตัว
ไม่ได้จะว่าอะไรนะ แต่พ่อไม่ชอบกวางเลย
โคตรน่าเบื่อเลย เยอะแยะไปหมด อย่างกับหนูแหนะ
พวกมันทำลายระบบนิเวศหมด ถ้าพ่อเห็นกวางตายตัวนึงนะ นั่นมันแค่จุดเริ่มต้น
แม่ยังไม่เข้าใจเลย - พ่อจะบอกว่า...
รู้อะไรมั้ย พ่อว่าดีละที่ลูกชนมันไป พ่อไม่ชอบพวกมันเลย
เข้าใจแล้วค่ะ
พวกลูกดู....เหนื่อยมาก
นิดหน่อยครับ
แล้วพวกลูก... เอ่อ... คบกับมานานแค่ไหนแล้ว
นานแค่ไหน?
4 เดือน  -  4  เดือน
5 ต่างหากล่ะ
เธอพูดถูกครับ ผมผิดเอง
เก่งมากลูกชาย ต้องฝึกพูดให้ชินนะ
แม่ขอโทษทีนะ
ขอโทษ .. แม่พูดถูก พ่อผิดเอง
เห็นมั้ย?
มีปุ่มปิดมั้ยคะ เล่นมุกกันซะเหนื่อยเลย
มา ให้พ่อพาเดินดูบ้าน
เอ่อ ขอไปเก็บของก่อนได้มั้ยคะ
อยากจะเก็บของ ก่อนเดินทัวร์อีกเหรอ ?
นี่ออฟฟิซของแม่เค้า เวลาตรวจคนไข้
แม่เป็นนักบำบัดเหรอครับ? - จิตแพทย์น่ะ
ดูเหมือนคนเมืองนี้จะบ้าๆ บอๆ เหมือนในเมืองนั่นแหละ
นี่ เจเรมี่ น้องชายของโรส
ผมเคยได้ยินโรสพูดถึง
เค้ากำลังเรียนหมออยู่ น่าจะอยากเป็นเหมือนพ่อ
เดี๋ยวก็เจอ  โอเคครับ
นี่ได้มาจากบาหลี
มันค่อนข้างปนๆกันนะ ผม เอ่อ ...
ผมเป็นนักเดินทาง ชอบเก็บของที่ระลึกมา
มันเป็นเหมือนสิทธิพิเศษที่จะเข้าใจวัฒนธรรมอื่นๆน่ะ นายเข้าใจไหม?
นี่เลย คุณต้องชอบมันแน่. สิ่งที่ทำให้พ่อผมมีชื่อเสียง
เขาแพ้ เจสซี โอเว่น ในรอบคัดเลือกโอลิมปิคที่เบอร์ลินปี 1936
เกมส์ที่.. -ที่โอเว่นชนะฮิตเลอร์
ใช่ สุดยอดไปเลย ฮิตเลอร์นั่งเอ๋ออยู่กับอารยานคนเก่งของเขา
แล้วคนดำคนนั้นก็ได้แสดงให้โลกเห็นว่าเขาคิดผิด เหลือเชื่อมาก
ขอโทษแทนพ่อคุณด้วยนะ .-ใช่ เขาเกือบจบเห่แล้วเหมือนกัน
ห้องใต้ดินนั้น เราต้องปิดมัน มันมีแต่ราดำเต็มไปหมด
แม่รักห้องครัวของเธอน่ะ เราเลยเก็บมันไว้ให้เธอ
จอเจียน่า นี้คริส แฟนของโรส
ว่าไง -สวัสดี
เศษอาหารมันลงไปในซิ้ง แล้ว..
main dish.
แล้วก็สนามหลังบ้าน
ฉันชอบบ้านที่ติดกับทะเลสาปน่ะ
มีความเป็นส่วนตัวดี
ฉันรู้ว่าเธอคิดอะไรอยู่ -ครับ?
ไม่เอาน่า ฉันรู้
ครอบครัวคนขาว คนใช้ผิวสี เหมือนสมัยก่อน
ผมไม่ได้คิดแบบนั้น -ใช่ ไม่ต้องหรอก เชื่อฉัน
เราจ้างจอร์เจียน่ากับวอร์เตอร์มาดูแลพ่อแม่
เมื่อแม่ฉันตาย มันก็ยากที่จะเลิกจ้างพวกเขา
แต่ฉันก็ไม่ชอบนะที่มันเป็นอย่างนี้
ครับ ผมรู้ว่าคุณหมายความว่ายังไง
อันท่ีจริง ฉันจะเลือกโอบาม่าอีกครั้งเลยนะถ้าทำได้
ประธานาธิบดีที่ดีที่สุดในชีวิตฉัันเลย
ผมเห็นด้วยเลย -ใช่
แล้วพ่อแม่เธอทำงานอะไร คริส?
ผมไม่ค่อยได้รู้จักพ่อเท่าไหร่ แม่ก็เสียตอนผมอายุ 11 ขวบ
โอ้ ฉันเสียใจด้วยนะ เธอเป็นอะไรถึงเสีย -ชนแล้วหนีน่ะครับ
แย่จริง
ฉันเสียใจด้วยจริงๆ -ตอนนั้นเธอยังเด็กมาก
อันที่จริงผมแทบจะจำไม่ได้แล้ว..
ไม่เป็นไร เราไม่ต้องคุยเรื่องนี้ละกัน
นายสูบไหม คริส?
สักตัวไหม? -ผมกำลังเลิกอยู่ครับ
พ่อ นี้แหละทำไมเราจึงเหลือกันแค่นี้
ไม่เป็นไร เราไม่ว่าอะไรหรอก -มันไม่ดีต่อสุขภาพ
มิสซี่ช่วยได้นะ -ยังไง?
สะกดจิตน่ะ ได้ผลดีมาก
บางคนก็ไม่อยากให้คนแปลกหน้ามาเอะอะโวยวายในหัวนะ
นี่คริสต์ ฉันเคยคิดว่าทั้งหมดนี่มันไร้สาระ
ฉันสูบบุหรี่มา15ปีแล้วก็มีความสุขทุกครั้งที่ได้สูบมัน
แต่เธอเคยสะกดจิตฉันครั้งหนึ่งแล้วฉันก็ยอมแพ้เลย
ใจเย็นๆ ดีน -เป็นเหมือนกับการรักษา
ขอผมลองหน่อยนะครับถ้ามีโอกาส
เอาล่ะ จะสูบไม่สูบเราก็ดีใจน่ะที่นายมางานรวมตัวครั้งใหญ่วันนี้
เดี๋ยวนะ วันนีวันหยุดเหรอ -จ้ะ
รวมตัวอะไร?  -โอ้ พระเจ้า
ขอบใจจ้ะ มันเป็นวันฉลองบรรพบุรุษของโรสน่ะ
พ่อของฉันจัดปาร์ตี้ทุกๆปี เชิญเพื่อนๆเขามารวมตัวกัน
เล่นบิลเลียต แบตมินตัน
เดี๋ยว ทำไมพ่อแม่ต้องบอกเรื่องนี้ด้วยล่ะคะ?
ก็เพราะมันจัดทุกปีในวันเดิมไงลูกรัก -ไม่จริงซักหน่อย
จริงๆ -ใช่
จริงเหรอ? -ไม่จริงซักหน่อย
พวกเขาพึ่งจากเราไป เรามารวมตัวกันเพื่อระลึก
ว่าพวกเขายังอยู่กับเรา
หนูแค่อยากได้วันหยุดที่สงบๆ -ไม่เอาน่า สนุกดีออก
ขอโทษค่ะ -จอร์เจียน่า?
ฉันขอโทษจริงๆค่ะ ดูสิฉันทำอะไรลงไปเนี่ย.. -ไม่เป็นไร
ทำไมไม่ไปพักสักหน่อยล่ะ?
ค่ะ ฉันก็ว่าดีเหมือนกัน -ดี
ว่าไงทุกคน?
ว่าไง
ว่าไงลูกรัก
มีใครไปเปิดประตูไหม?
ว่าไง โรสซี่
ทำไมต้องโกหกด้วยล่ะ? -ดี
เธอเคยบอกนายเรื่องคอลเลกชั่นเล็บเท้าไหม?
อะไรนะ? -โอ้ พระเจ้า
เธอกัดแล้วก็อมแล้วก็เอาใส่กล่องเครื่องประดับ
ฉันไม่รู้เรื่องเลย พูดเรื่องอะไรกัน -ขนลุกสุดๆเลย
ฉันเกลียดนาย -โอเค เรื่องนี้ก็เด็ดเหมือนกัน
เรื่องนี้ตอนโรสอยู่ปีหนึ่ง
โรสเคยชอบคอนเนอร์ การ์ฟิลล์ -ไม่
คอนเนอร์ การ์ฟิลล์ -ไม่ใช่นะแม่
ไม่เอาน่าเจเรมี พอได้แล้ว
ไม่ๆเอาเลยผมอยากฟัง -โรส อย่าเสียมารยาทสิลูก
แขกของเราเขาอยากฟัง เล่าเลย -ขอบคุณครับ
คอนเนอร์คนั้นอยู่ในทีมลาร์คอส ตัวใหญ่เกือบ2 เมตร แต่โง่ไปหน่อย
แล้วเราก็จัดปาร์ตี้ -นายจัดปาร์ตี้เหรอ
ตอนนั้นพ่อแม่ไปกรีซ
เรามีเหล้าเป็นกระบุงและก็เมามากด้วย
บอกฉันสิโรสว่ามันไม่จริง
ฉันเติมน้ำเปล่าลงในขวด
เล่าต่อเลยลูก -โอเค
ผมอยู่กับสาวสวยที่สุดในชั้น จีน ดีลีย์
รู้มั้ยตอนนี้นายมันงี่เง่าที่สุดในโลกแล้วตอนนี้
คอนเนอร์เริ่มเคาะประตูห้องน้ำ ฉันเลยเปฺิด..
เลือดพุ่งออกมาจากปากเขา แล้วเขาก็คำรวมว่าพี่สาวแกกัดลิ้นฉัน!
คุณกัดลิ้นเขา?
จริงๆแล้วมันเป็นจูบแรกของฉัน แล้วเขาก็สอดลิ้นเข้ามา...
แล้วฉันก็ไม่ได้ตั้งใจมันเป็นปฏิกิริยาตอบโต้อัตโนมัติน่ะ
ฉันไม่เคยเรียนมาก่อนเลยว่ามีปฏิกิริยาตอบโต้อัตโนมัติแบบนี้ด้วย
Yeah, you better be careful. - Yes, very carefully now.
I'll get dessert. And Dean, maybe you want to clean it up a little bit?
Chris, what's your sport? Football? Basketball? - Basketball, especially ...
Are you an MMA fan?
Guy. - Dude, what?
What?
Hey, Jeremy, why not just let someone else speak.
You're going to my sister?
He's with my sister. You had your chance.
I may not know him?
You mean like UFC?
Yes. - Too violent for me.
Have you ever entered a street fight as a child?
I did judo after school, first grade. You should have seen me.
Judo?
Because with your construction and genetic makeup ...
if you get really out of your body ...
And I mean not just work out what to do, you'd be a damned beast.
Carrotcake.
What have I missed?
A whole lot of nothing. - We just chatted about sports.
Yet? - Yes.
That sounds good.
So the thing is with jiujitsu ...
that strength does not matter.
It has to do with this.
It is a strategy game, like chess.
You have two, three, four put forward thinking.
Cool.
Stand up.
Jeremy, no karate at the dinner table. - It is not karate, Mom.
I have a rule: no sparring with drunks.
Not spar? I just want to...
I did not hurt him.
He wanted to take you in a headlock.
What's his problem? He has never been dealt with my friends. Never.
And my father that "my husband" then.
My husband. He has never heard or said to me ...
and now that is all he says.
And my mother was so rude to Georgina? Why was that? It was so crazy.
They still do the same as agent?
That's so fucking sorry.
Would you do anything else to say?
I told you so.
I did not say it.
I hate to be wrong.
I noticed. - But I'm sorry.
No. Wait. Come here. - Sorry. This sucks.
What? Why do you say that?
Because I brought you here and I'm related to them.
No, it's fine.
Why are you so quiet? - Honestly, this is nothing.
I think you like as your current varieties.
Is this a racial power? - Variety Power.
I feel a racial power. - Yes, you feel rassenstromig.
What? - The party.
How bad can that be? - They're so white.
But really so white. - It will be fine.
You know, with my genetic makeup the shit goes down. I'm a beast.
Do you realize how dangerous smoking is?
And.
Come sit with me. Here you go.
Just for a moment. Here you go.
Thanks.
Is it comfortable enough? - Its perfect. Thanks.
No problem.
Want to know how it works?
You dangling a pocket watch in front of someone's face? Is that it?
You watch too much TV. - When I was little.
Now you feel very sleepy.
We sometimes use focal points ...
to put someone in a state of heightened suggestibility.
Increased suggestibility? - That's right.
Do you smoke at my daughter?
I'll stop, I promise. - That's my child.
Are you interested?
What about your mother?
How do you mean?
Wait, we're ... - Where were you when she died?
I do not think.
Home ... to watching TV.
Hear the TV?
What do you hear?
Rain. - Rain. It rained.
Can you hear the rain?
Do you hear it? Find it.
Tell me when you've found it.
Come here, Chris, look at me.
I found it. - Where was your mother?
That...
was on his way home. She was not home.
Her work?
And what did you do?
Nothing.
Nothing?
I just sat there.
Did you call anyone? - No.
Why not?
I do not know, I ...
thought that if I did, it would be true.
You're so scared.
Do you think it was your fault?
How do you feel now?
I can not move.
You can not move. - Why can not I move?
You're paralyzed.
Like that day when you did nothing. You did nothing.
Not...
zinc in the floor.
Wait. - Zinc.
Now you're in the Sunken Spot.
How is it going?
They make you work hard here.
Nothing I do not want to do.
I have not personally met yet. I'm Chris.
I know who you are.
She is beautiful.
Rose?
Yes, she is beautiful. - One in a million. From the top shelf.
A real stayer.
Right.
I'm sorry about last night. - What?
My exercise. I did not mean to scare you.
And has it worked? - What?
You were a long time in the office of Mrs Armitage.
I think I got drunk last night too. Can not really remember, so ...
Well, I must get back to work and I interfere in my affairs.
I think your mother has hypnotized me last night.
What? When?
I went to go outside for some fresh air and I met her and ...
and I remember almost nothing not, but does the thought of a cigarette surrender ...
Oh my God.
Sorry. I can not believe she did that.
And I had weird dreams. - What did you dream?
I was in a hole or something and I could not move. It was like ...
That sounds awful. Sorry.
What happened to Walter?
What do you mean?
I just spoke with him. And he did very hostile. - Did he say anything?
It's not what he says but how.
Maybe he likes you.
Maybe he's jealous or something. I...
Are you kidding me? - No.
So you think I stand a chance with him?
Okay, you find that funny. - Do you have a good word?
Great, no, fine. - I talk about it with my father. That is not...
Do not do that. It's okay. - No, that's not it.
It is all right. It does not matter. Forget it. It has happened.
O jee.
Damn.
It begins. Are you ready for it?
Yes. - Not me.
There they are. Marcia.
So much fun.
Just laugh. - Laugh? Okay. How do you do that again?
Just smile all the time. Yes, that's right. There it is.
Look, the Greene's.
Gordon and Emily, this is Chris. Chris, this is Gordon and Emily Greene.
Nice to meet you, Chris.
Indeed nice to meet you. - Also.
That's quite a grip. - Thank you. You too.
Do you play golf?
Once, a few years ago. I was not really good.
Gordon was a professional golfer for years. - Are you serious?
I can not run as well on the hips. But I know Tiger.
That's fantastic. - Super.
Gordon loves Tiger. - The best I've ever seen, hands down.
Let's look at your condition.
These Nelson and Lisa. - How are you?
How handsome he is?
Are you pretty?
Not bad, Nelson?
Is it true?
Is it better?
Fair skin had the last hundred years is preferred.
But now that's changing. Dark is fashionable.
Excuse me. I'm going to take a few pictures. - Of course.
There he is.
Nice to see another brother here.
Hi. Yes of course.
Is something wrong?
There you are. Do something with this.
Hey. I'm Philomena. And you are?
Chris. Rose's boyfriend.
Fantastic. You are a lovely couple.
Thanks. - Where are my manners? Logan. Logan King.
Chris just told me that he felt more comfortable in my presence.
That's nice.
Logan, I hate to have to take you but Wincotts asked about you.
Well, it was nice meeting you, Chris.
Day.
What?
Ignorance.
Who? - Everyone here.
They mean well, but they have no idea what real people experience.
Jim Hudson.
- Chris.
I know who you are.
I am an admirer of your work. You have a great eye.
Wait. Jim Hudson? Hudson Galleries?
Believe me, the irony of being blind art dealer, does not escape me.
How do you do it?
My assistant's work describes in great detail to me.
You've got something.
The images you capture are so brutal, so melancholic.
Powerful stuff. I think.
Thanks.
I took pictures used to be. Mostly wilderness.
I have 14-fold submitted to "Nat Geo" before I realized I was not good enough.
When I started selling it and then my vision for soap.
I know. Life can be a bad joke.
One day you will develop into a dark room, the next day you wake up in the dark.
Genetic disease.
Life is not fair, man. - You're quite right. Life is not fair.
Come here.
What is it? You left me there alone? - Look at this.
She pulled my phone out of the socket. - Who?
Georgina. I came here to talk to Rod and now the battery is empty.
And why should she have done? - Maybe she does not like ...
I'm your friend.
Really?
It's a thing.
So, you're so sexy that people so get your phone out of the socket?
Never mind. - No, stop. Do ...
Do not do that. Do ... - I'm sorry. It's okay.
They enable you are already on display.
It's weird, man. And the people here.
Like they never saw a dark man, who does not work for them.
I. Ze show is.
And I want to tell you that not even. - What?
I was hypnotized last night. - Get out there.
No. To quit smoking. But Rose's mother is a psychiatrist, so ...
Even though that bitch Iyanla Vanzant, right?
She can not make my life better. You're not in my head.
I know. I saw it coming. But it's okay, because ...
I am cured. It worked. - Why are not you afraid?
They had you in to let you do anything. They can make you bark like a dog ...
or fly around like a fucking pigeon, and then you'd have looked stupid. Or...
I do not know if you know this. White people like to make people sex slaves.
I'm pretty sure they are not weird sex family.
Look, Jeffrey Dahmer ate the heads of Negroes. Okay? But that was after he had fucked heads.
Do you think they saw that coming? Not really.
They went there thinking they had a sucking dick and had to play with some balls.
No. They could play with anything because their head was not on their bodies.
They still sucked the dick, but without their head. That was damn weird.
นั่นคือ เจฟฟรีย์ ดาห์เมอร์
ขอบคุณสำหรับภาพน่ะ
ผมไม่ได้ทำน่ะ ผมเห็นมันที่ A & E
นั้นเรื่องจริง
และคนผิวสีที่นี่พวกเขาทำเหมือนไม่รู้ไม่เห็นอะไรเลย
นั้นอาจเป็นเพราะว่าพวกเขากำลังถูกสะกดจิตอยู่ก็ได้
ดูสิ ผมแค่จะปะติดปะต่อเรื่อง ผมเริ่มจากสิ่งที่คุณบอกกับผม
และผมจะบอกให้น่ะ ผมคิดว่าแม่งจะทำให้ทุกคนมึนงงแล้วจากนั้นค่อยควบคุมกับสมองของพวกเขา
ขอบคุณน่ะ ร็อด ลาก่อน
ฮาโหล  เฮ้ย
I owe you my apologies.
It was rude of me to touch your things without asking.
No, it's okay. I was just confused.
I can assure you it was not intentional.
Let me explain.
I lifted your mobile to clean the dresser ...
and the plug was accidentally cord.
I thought it better not to come further on so I left it that way.
How silly of me.
It's okay. I did not tell on you.
Tattle? - betray you.
Click Particle.
Do not worry about it.
I can assure you...
I have to be accountable to anyone.
Right.
I just know I get nervous when there are too many whites.
You owe me there alone.
So I do not experience it. Not at all.
The Armitages so good for us.
They treat us like family.
That bitch is crazy.
Wait a second. Chris, I want you to meet some friends.
These are David and Marcia Wincott, Ronald and Celia Jeffries ...
Hiroki Tanaka en Jessika en Fredrich Walden.
Too many names to remember, but hi.
Like his African-American ...
more advantage or disadvantage in the modern world?
That's a tough one.
Yeah, I do not know.
She asked me about the African American experience. Maybe you can answer that.
The African-American experience for me for the most part been very good.
Although it is difficult to go into detail ...
because I for a while do not want to go outside.
We have become house sparrows.
But even if you go into town, I just do not feel.
The chores have become my sanctuary.
Smeer 'em.
Sorry, man.
Go away.
Quiet. - Spread 'em.
Quiet.
Seizures create anxiety, which can lead to aggression.
Yes, but randomly attack people? - It was not random.
It was your flashlight. This gave him the attack.
How is he doing? - Much better.
I think that I...
should apologize.
No, we're just glad you're yourself again.
Yes that's me.
And I thank God that you have calmed me.
I realize that I've scared you a little. Especially you, Chris.
I'm sorry.
The flashlight, which I did not.
Of course not. How was that?
But you also should not drink.
Good. I will let you celebrate the rest of the evening without the help of my wonderful wit.
The whole ordeal has exhausted me.
Why do not you rest a bit?
It was nice meeting you, Chris.
Something to improve the mood?
Yes. Let's start this party again.
What do you think of stars and bingo?
We are going for a walk. - Are you sure?
Shall we?
My cousin has epilepsy. That was not an attack.
My father is a neurosurgeon and according to him it was an attack.
I trust him ... - It was not an attack.
What was it?
How long have you known him?
From today. Why?
This will sound crazy, but ...
when he attacked me ...
I felt that I knew him.
Logan like you've already met? - No, not Logan, but the man who attacked me.
I think your mother has been in my head.
She has been in my head.
Yes, and I thought it worked. - No, it did not work.
She was in my head and now I think all those weird thoughts I do not want to think.
Like what?
I have to get out of here.
You want to leave.
Without me.
Whatever you want.
I told you about that night when my mother died.
When I called 911 not and did not find her.
An hour passed, then two ... three ...
and I just sat there.
I was just watching TV.
There was nothing you could do. - I later found out that ...
She had survived the first blow.
She lay there bleeding along the side of the road, cold and alone.
They died in the early morning, cold and alone.
And I was watching TV.
You were just a little kid. - There was time.
There was time.
There was a time when someone was looking for her. There was time, but no one was looking.
You're all I have. I'm not leaving here without you. I will not let you down.
No? - No, I do not.
Goodness, you scared me.
Let's go home.
What?
Let's go home. Because this sucks.
This sucks. Let's go home. I'll think of something.
I love you.
Love you too darling.
Bye. - Come on, baby.
Goodbye, Chris. It was great to meet you.
Asshole.
That's Dre. - Dre ?
Andre Hayworth.
Did it with Veronica? - Veronica what?
Teresa's sister who worked on the 8th in the cinema.
Yes that is him. But wait.
This is so damn mad.
He's different. - Really.
Why is he dressed like that? - That's not it. It's everything.
He came to the party with a white woman who was 30 years older.
Sex Slave.
Chris, you have there. you are in an " Eyes Wide Shut " situation. Go away...
you go a ... Hello?
Chris? Its battery will be empty.
Hey handsome. Are you packing? - Rose, we have to leave now.
Is everything alright?
I tell you in the car but we have to go now. Is that okay?
Okay. Yes. I'll get my purse.
Are you ready? - Yes, I was looking for my camera.
The is here.
Do you have the keys? I quickly put the bags in the trunk.
They're here somewhere. I need to find them yet.
Are you OK?
I've so.
Can not find your keys?
No. I can never find. - We do this move.
Chris ... - Grab those keys.
Where are you going? The party is just starting. - I just put the bags in the car, man.
Anyone for tea? - No thanks. We leave, actually.
Really? Why? Is there something wrong?
His dog was very ill, so he will have tomorrow morning to the vet.
Sorry. - How terrible.
Rose, the keys. - I'm looking for.
What is your goal, Chris?
What?
In life. What is your target?
At present, that finding those keys. Yes?
Brand.
It is a reflection of our own mortality.
We are born, we breathe and then we die.
I am searching.
Even the sun will die one day.
But we are divine.
We are the gods trapped in cocoons.
I do not know where they are.
Rose, give me those keys. Rose, give me ...
Give me those keys. Rose, now. The keys.
Careful. - What?
I have done nothing. - What the hell is going on?
Where are the keys, Rose?
You know I can not give.
Come on.
Is he injured? - Did you see him go down?
Yes. Jeremy, grab his legs, please. Bring him down. Dean, help him.
I can only carry him.
No, you've damaged him enough. - Alright.
Are you ready? - Watch his head.
Careful.
You'll drop him. - No, it is not.
You're not me ...
Can I help? - Okay, that was my fault.
You were one of my favorites.
You hear that, Chris?
One of her favorites.
Hi, it's Chris. Or am I not in the phone or I just do not want to talk to you. Peace.
Yes. Me too.
The mind is wasting something terrible.
Millions of Americans feel the effects of aging.
Every movement puts pressure on your joints.
Over time, this wear can cause discomfort.
What happened to Andre Hayworth? He disappeared in Evergreen Hallow
Is there anything more beautiful than a sunrise?
I am Roman Armitage and if you look here, you're probably wondering what happens.
You do not worry. Let's take a walk.
You're chosen for its physical benefits that you have all enjoyed your whole life.
With your natural gifts and our determination we can both be part of something bigger.
Something perfect.
The Coagula procedure is a miracle created by man.
Our order which has been developing for many years ...
and has only recently been perfected ...
by my own flesh and blood.
My family and I are honored to be offered as a service to members of our group.
Do not waste your strength. Do not fight it. You can not stop the inevitable.
And who knows?
Perhaps you will one day enjoy yourself to be a member of the family.
Behold ...
coagulants.
What?
Hallo, meneer...?
- Williams. Rod Williams.
TSA? - Yes Madam.
You know that all of TSA issues should go through the competent officer.
Yes, ma'am, but this is not a TSA issue.
Do not call me "ma'am." Because we can not get along.
How can I help you, Rod Williams of the TSA? - Okay, that's it.
My Chris has been missing for two days.
Your son is missing? - No. Not my son. My friend. He was 26.
His name is Chris Washington.
He left Friday with his girlfriend, Rose Armitage.
She is Caucasian.
Okay, go ahead. - Look, Chris would return Sunday.
And I pass on his dog, Sid.
That's Sid. - Cute, right?
Chris sent me this from the house of the parents of his girlfriend.
You see? That's Andre Hayworth.
Okay? Someone we knew before.
Apparently he has been missing for six months in such affluent suburb.
He looks not missing out. - That's because we found him. Right?
But Chris says he behaves differently.
How else? - He's from Brooklyn. He does not dress like that.
I dressed once not so, but ...
He is married to a white woman who is twice as old.
And that would explain the clothes. Okay.
Rod Williams, TSA.
I know, but I try to explain it.
What I will tell you, is going to sound crazy. Are you ready?
Say it. - I think they abduct dark people ...
they brainwash them and so make it work for them as sex slaves or so.
Sorry about that. Sorry.
Wait a second.
Then he sent me a funny picture, and I think, 'Oh dear, that's Andre Hayworth. "
Which has been missing for six months.
So I research everything because if a TSA agent got the same training as you.
Sometimes we might know more than you because we are dealing with terrorists, so ...
But that's another story. So I do my research ...
and I begin to put the pieces together and this is where I came in.
I think they abduct dark people, they brainwash and enslave them ...
or seksslaven not only ordinary slaves, but seksslaven or so.
Look, I do not know whether the hypnosis is making them slaves ...
but I know they have two brothers and they might have been more.
What is the next step?
And never say that I do nothing for you.
White girls do it every time.
เวทมนต์ไม่มีจริง
นี่มันไม่สมเหตุสมผลเลย
สวัสดี
How are you, Rose? It's me, Rod. - Hi.
คริส อยู่ไหน
He left two days ago. - He left?
Yes. He became completely paranoid and went against me furiously.
And when he got into a taxi and forgot his phone.
Wait. You have not seen him? - No, he has not come home.
I have often called him. I even went to the police.
What did you say? - I just said he was missing.
Good. You ...
May I ask you something.
he left with what taxi company?
Heavens, I ...
I do not know. Perhaps a local or perhaps an Uber.
Wait, I'm so confused.
You're confused? You know, me too.
Can you wait? Okay, moment.
Lying bitch. They lie like a damn ... I know ...
TSA thing itches. This lying bitch.
Okay, I got you. I'm going to record.
I'm going to record lies. You talk too much. You'll say anything.
Record.
Speaker.
Not silent.
So the last time I talked to Chris, he said your mother had hypnotized him.
Rod, love it.
I know why you're calling. - Why?
It's pretty obvious, is not it?
What?
That there is something between us.
No, what are you talking about? I called you about Chris.
No, Rod, every time we went out, I remember you looked at me.
What? No, Chris is my best friend.
If you have done something to him ..
- I know you want to fuck me, Rod.
Nobody thinks that. Why do you say that nonsense? What...
Bitch. I did not fuck you. Bye.
God, she's so ... she's a damn ... She's ... She's a genius.
เ้ดี๋ยว
Hi, Chris. How you doing, buddy?
You can answer, there is an intercom in the room.
Where is Rose? - You dirty dog.
You're one of the lucky ones, believe me.
Jeremy's difficult method sounds much less pleasant.
I need all outstanding questions or concerns that you have so far answered.
Apparently our common understanding of the process ...
a positive effect on the success of the procedure.
You do not give a ball. Let me just explain what it is.
The first phase was the hypnosis. They numb you.
Phase two is this. Mental preparation. It is actually a psychological pre-op.
Pre-op? - For stage three.
Transplantation.
Well, partially, actually.
The piece of your brains being connected must stay on your nervous system ...
to keep intact those complicated connections.
So you do not die. At least not completely.
A little piece of you will still be somewhere inside. Limited consciousness.
You'll be able to see and hear ...
What does your body, but you will still only be a passenger.
An audience. You will live in ...
- The Sunken Spot.
Now you're in the Sunken Spot.
Yes. For example, she calls it.
I will check the motor function, so I'm ...
Me.
You'll be mine.
Good.
เรียนรู้เร็วนิ ดีแล้ว
ทำไมถึงเป็นเรา
ทำไมต้องคนดำ
ใครรู้บ้าง
People want change. Some people want to be stronger ... faster ... victim.
Dark is fashionable.
But I'm not. It makes me not give a shit what color you have.
No, what I want is deeper.
I want your eyes, man.
I want those things that you look.
This is madness.
Okay, I'm done.
Asshole.
You ...
Come on.
One Mississippi, two Mississippi ...
three Mississippi, four Mississippi ...
911. What is your emergency?
- I'm in the house Armitage. My name is Chris.
I'm sorry, sir, can you repeat that?
I'm in ... I'm in Armitage ...
No, do not. Just go away.
His.
You have destroyed my house.
Pak hem, opa.
Let me do it.
I'm so sorry.
It's me.
I love you.
ช่วย
ช่วยฉันด้วย
ฉันบอกคุณแล้วอย่าไปบ้านหลังนั้น
I mean...
How did you find me?
I'm TS fucking A.
We arrange things.
That's what we do.
Consider this situation ...
if handled.
Vertaling:
Quality over Quantity (QoQ) Releases
www.thaisubtitle.com
บรรยายไทยโดย
PTR, Greatpoppy1502, BEAMBOYZ, emo00123, Desolution
forte1412, nutrockertvkub, cdimq, 1z2z3z4z5z, dirtydog